<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="alex">ALEX BRANOM\n
        HEAD MUAY THAI INSTRUCTOR\n
        Alex Branom started with the original Team Quest in 2003 and received his purple belt under
        Eddie Bravo in 2011. He also spent some time in Thailand, where he traveled and trained
        throughout the country. He is a Rajanderm Stadium veteran and has trained with legendary Jean
        Wayne Parr, Saenchai sor Koingstar, Pornsehnee Sitmonchai, and Hongthonglex, the best of the
        best in Muay Thai. He graduated from Team Quest’s instructors’ course in 2007 and has been
        coaching since 2008. In the past four years, he has competed in 14 Muay Thai matches. Now
        that he is back in the US, he has been focusing on his MMA career and developing his Muay
        Thai for MMA.</string>
    <string name="robin">ROBIN WOODS\n
        OPERATIONS MANAGER AND COACH\n
        Robin is a mixed martial arts (MMA) fighter in Portland, OR and the owner of World Class
        Athletics. Robin first got exposed to MMA through kickboxing and fitness classes in 2006.
        In 2011 she took her first fight and has since distinguished herself as one of the top 125lb
        female fighters in the region. She was the FCFF Female Fighter of the Year in 2011 and also
        received the FCFF Most Unique Finish 2013 for her powerbomb slam knockout of Katie Howard.
        She began competing in Muay Thai in 2016 and is looking to begin a professional boxing career
        in the near future.  Robin is also a member of the Oregon Rugby Sports Union Women’s Premier
        League team, a player on the Portland Hunters touch rugby team, and a coach for the Reed
        Men’s and Women's Rugby teams.</string>
    <string name="rachel">RACHEL SODERBERG\n
        STRENGTH AND CONDITIONING COACH\n
        In February 2013, Rachel began training under Lyman Hiter with CrossFit Immense in Clackamas,
        Oregon and has since expanded her fitness career to include over two dozen obstacle racing
        events including a half-marathon trail tire carry challenge, long-distance obstacle course
        races, and 12+ hour endurance events such as Spartan Race and Tough Mudder. As of February
        2017 she has logged over 200 miles of street and obstacle course races. Through Clackamas
        Community College and Oregon Institute of Technology, Rachel has taken several Nutrition and
        wellness courses as well as Kung-Fu and Tai Chi. She began the second level of her training
        under Robin Woods at World Class Athletics in April 2015 and was brought on as one of the
        Strength and Conditioning coaches in 2016, providing her clients with the skills necessary
        to meet their own nutrition and fitness-related goals. Recently Rachel has added Muay Thai,
        under Alex Branom, to her list of athletic endeavors and strives to improve herself every
        single day.</string>
</resources>