<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="styles">STYLES\n
        Muay Khao - Overpowering strength and devastating knees.\n
        Muay Mat - Aggressive, heavy punches and kicks. Charges forward.\n
        Muay Feemue (Femur) - Technical fighter. Highly skilled and works angles.
    </string>
    <string name="weapons">WEAPONS\n
        Fists are the most-used mid-range weapons; the lead fist is considered the quicker but less-
        powerful of the two while the rear fist is often the go-to power technique. Power and
        explosiveness is generated by turning over the hips and feet with each strike.\n
        Elbow attacks are a valuable weapon both in and out of the clinch, used in close-range much
        like a knife to slice and cut the opponent and potentially end a fight altogether.\n
        Knees are used to spear the opponent, generating enough force to knock a person unconscious.
        Strikes from the knees are most commonly used from the clinch, but have uses anywhere from
        close- to mid-range.\n
        Kicks can be the most devastating of all the weapons. A well-timed Push Kick or Teep is used
        similarly to a jab both offensively and defensively, but the Roundhouse Kick is the kicking
        technique used most often in Muay Thai. Like the swinging of a baseball bat, the entire body
        is thrown behind the kick: the legs, hips, core, and arms rotate with the body to create a
        force unmatched by any other strike.
    </string>
    <string name="defense">SELF DEFENSE\n
        The Push Kick, or Teep, works well to put distance between you and your attacker, often
        stunning them if the timing is right.\n
        Throwing a knee can be devastating in close quarters, use this to the belly or groin if the
        attacker has a hold on your arms or around you.\n
        Along with the knee, one can enter the Clinch to remove the attacker\'s control of their head
        and posture while minimizing the damage you receive. From the Clinch you may throw elbows and
        knees; an unskilled person will attempt to duck/drop out and open themselves up to knees to
        their face.\n
        Elbows can leave cuts and significant bruising; these are very effective in close quarters.
    </string>
</resources>